Guide to the Stanford University, Haas Center for Public Service, Records SC0541
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-2001-237
  - Posters, Subseries 8
    - You Can Make a Difference - Public Service Center poster, undated (Box 19)
    - You Can Make a Difference Conference poster, January 31, 1987 (Box 19)
    - You Can Make a Difference Conference poster, November 12-15, 1987 (Box 19)
    - You Can Make a Difference Conference poster, January 18-20, 1990 (Box 19)
    - You Can Make a Difference Conference poster, January 26, 1991 (Box 19)
    - You Can Make a Difference Conference poster, February 1, 1992 (Box 19)
    - You Can Make a Difference Conference poster, April 24, 1993 (Box 19)
    - You Can Make a Difference Conference poster April 2, 1995 (Box 19)
    - AD Conference poster, April 27, 1996 (Box 19)
  - Restricted Files, Subseries 9
    - Haas Professorship Search Files, 1998 (Box 18)
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-2003-197
  - East Palo Alto Project Files, Subseries 1
    - Documents and Reports Lists (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
    - Documents and Reports Leads / Sources (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - List of Documents (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Economics, Nairobi Shopping Center – Report to make recommendations to reverse retail "leakage" 7/75 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Economics, Table 1: [Poverty] Characteristics of EPH compared to San Mateo County 5/78 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Economics, Nairobi (PMC) Shopping Center Study 8/7/78 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Economics, Economics and Fiscal Impact Analysis of the East Palo Alto Community Plan 4/81 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Economics / Land Use / Environment, Cooley Landing Marina Feasibility Study 9/81 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Economics / Environment / Land Use, Draft Environmental Impact Report – East Palo Alto Redevelopment Project Area Boundary Amendment – 1987 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Economics, Economics Development Assessment (East Palo Alto 9/83), National Conference of Black Mayors, Inc. (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Economics, Housing, "Toward an Economic Development Strategy for East Palo Alto, California," CDI Report, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 12/86, Economic, Environment, City of East Palo Alto, Plan (Box 1, Folder 13-14)
    - 5/11/89, Economic Development, Ashley Boren, Research (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - 7/89, Economics Development, Pannell, Kerr, Forster, Plan (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - 11/30/99, Economics, City of East Palo Alto, Research (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - 1989, Economics Redevelopment, Pryde, Roberts, Carr, Inc., Research (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - 1989, Economic Development, Research (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - 1989, Economic Development, Pryde Roberts, Carr, Inc., research (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - 6/90, Economics Redevelopment, City of East Palo Alto, Plan (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - 6/12/90, Economic, Stanford University Graduate School of Business, Plan (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - 7/90, Economic Redevelopment, East Palo Alto Redevelopment Agency, Plan (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - 1990, Economic, US Census, Report (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - 1990, Economics, US Census, Research (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - 6/15/93, Economics Redevelopment, Burns, Watry, Inc. Plan (Box 1, Folder 26-27)
    - 8/93, Economics, City of East Palo Alto, Plan (1 of 3) (Box 1, Folder 28-30)
    - 8/2/93, economics Redevelopment, Wallace, Roberts, Todd, Plan (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - 8/3/93, Economics Redevelopment, Economic Developmental Task Force, Research (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - 10/93, Economics Redevelopment, Burns, Watry, Inc., Plan (Box 1, Folder 33-35)
    - 10/23/93, Economics Development, Wallace, Roberts, Todd, Plan (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - 11/23/93, Economics Redevelopment, Economic Developmental Task Force, Research (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - 4/94, Economic, City of East Palo Alto, Plan (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - 4/94, Economics Development, East Palo Alto, Research (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - 6/4/94, Economic Development, Maillee Ferguson, Research (Box 1, Folder 40-41)
    - 11/17/95, Economics, Redevelopment, SF Chronicle, Loss of $900,000, Parcel Tax (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - 1/3/96, Economic development, SJ Mercury: "2 Seek to build…" (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - 1/22/96, Economic Development, East Palo Alto Zoning, Plan (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - 7/11/96, Economic Environment, Cotton Beland Associates, Plan (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Economics, East Palo Alto Peninsula Partnership Planning Group, Five Year Plan 1996 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - 2/97, Economics Development, City of East Palo Alto Redevelopment Agency, Plan (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - 3/29/97, Economics, San Jose Mercury, Journalist Manlee Enge, Research (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - 5/14/97, Economic, Sandra Sobiera, Associated Press, Research (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - 10/15/97, Economic, CA Employment Development Department, Research (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - 12/17/97, Economics Redevelopment, Brownfields Stakeholders Group, Plan (Box 1, Folder 51-52)
    - Economic redevelopments, Redevelopmental Agency and City Council, Plan (Box 1, Folder 53-54)
    - 3/18/1998, Economic, S.F. Chronicle, Michael McCrabe, Research (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - 3/24/98, Economics Development, JM Consulting Group, Inc., Plan (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - 5/98, Economics Development, East Palo Alto Redevelopment Agency, Plan (Box 1, Folder 57)
    - 1998, Economics Development, ABAC, Research (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - Economics, Community Capital Investment Initiative, letter asking for Mayor Jones' support 8/2/99 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Economics, After the Flood Waters Receded: Assessing the Economic Impacts of San Francisquito Creek’s February 1998 Flooding (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Economics; East Palo Alto Can Do Business Directory 1999 (Spanish) (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Spring 1999, Economics, Department of City and Regional Planning UC Berkeley, Plan (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Economics, East Palo Alto shopping for retailers (Good Guys) (San Jose Mercury article, 5/31/99) (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Economics, "East Palo Alto budget grows $1 million to over $11 million," San Mateo County Times, 6/15/99 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Economics, Business Needs and Capacity Assessment 9/99, City of East Palo Alto, Enterprise Foundation (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Economics, Business needs and Capacity Assessment: Final Report Summary 9/99, City of East Palo Alto, Enterprise Foundation (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - 4/5/00, Economic Development, "East Palo Alto Lands Ikea Store" (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - 8/5/2000, Economic Development, SF Chron. "Peninsula could get…" (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - 12/6/00, Economics and education, Metro Active News, S. Douglas (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - 4/8/01, Economic Redevelopment S.F. Mercury, "Residents…" (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Economics, East Palo Alto’s Opportunity by East Palo Alto city managers Office (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Economic, Jennifer Mena, San Jose Mercury News, Research (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Economic, Journalist Carolyne Zinko, Chronicle Peninsula Bureau, Research (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Economics, Journalist Dan Kazak, Research (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Economics Redevelopment, The City of East Palo Alto, Plan (1 of 3) (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Economics Redevelopment, The City of East Palo Alto, Plan (2 of 3) (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Economics Redevelopment, The City of East Palo Alto, Plan (3 of 3) (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Redevelopment, Research (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Redevelopment, California Redevelopment Association, Research (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - 12/1/97, Educational Enrollment Levels, SM County Office of Education, Research (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Economics, Redwood City, Budget at a Glance 1998-2000 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Educational Perf / Attainment / Population Numbers, research (Box 2, Folder 24-25)
    - Spring 1999, Educational Performance – Youth, California Department of Education, Research (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - 1976, Education (Youth), Ravenswood High School, Research (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - 10/85, Education Youth, CDI, Research (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Education Citations (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - 9/89, Education, Robert Lowe, Research (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - 4/91, Education: Youth, Community Ventures, Plan (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - 1995, Education Youth, US Census Bureau, Research (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Edu. Perf., Edu Att., Leslie Weinfield, Research (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - 1995, Educational Performance, The Children’s Preservation Network, Research (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - 12/96, Educational Performance, Research (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - 2/99, Educational Performance, Sequoia Union High School District, Research (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - 1/96, Education, The Written Word, Research (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - 8/26/96, Education, Elizabeth Yee, Research (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - 4/14/97, Education, CA Dept of Education, Research (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - 4/23/97, Education, San Francisco Chronicle, Research (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - 6/98, housing, City of East Palo Alto, Plan (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - 98, Public Safety, East Palo Alto Police Department, Research (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - 98, Public Safety, East Palo Alto Police Department, Research (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - 8/98, Education Youth, Sequoiz Union High School District, Research (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - 1/5/99, Education, San Mateo Office of education, Research (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - 2/1/99, Education, Professional Research Consultants, Inc., Research (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - 2/25/99, Education, Heather Augney, Research (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - 2/99, Educational Performance, Instructional Support and Student Assessment, Research (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - 4/16/99, Education, Jill Tucker, Research (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - May 1999, Education, Sequoia union HS district (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - 6/30/99, Education, http://novel.nifl.gov/newworld/correct.htm, Research (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - 9/8/99, Education Youth, CFFC Steering Committee Research (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - 5/1/01, Education, Realizations (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - 4/10/2001, Education, "Teaching or Trivia" SJ Mercury (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - 6/28/01, Education, SJ Mercury, "Schools Chief Benefits" (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - Education, National Institute for Literacy, Research (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - Education Youth, California Department of Education After School Program, Plan (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - Education Attainment, CA Dept. of Finance, Research (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - Educational Performance and Attainment, Palm School District, Research (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - Education, National Institute for Literacy, Research (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - Educational Performance Test Scores, Edwin Garcia, Research (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - Education youth, San Mateo County, Research (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - Education Attainment, Youth and Adults, Mary Hoover, Research (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - Educational Performance Rankings, Elizabeth Darling, Research (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - Educational Performance And Attainment, Role of Government, Research (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - Educational Performance, Educ. Attainment, Ravenswood Sequoia School Districts, Research (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - Educational Performance, Educ. Attainment, Upward Bound, Research (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - Education Attainment, Drop out rates, Elizabeth Darling, Research (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - Educational Performance, Educ. Attainment, Project Adelante, Research (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - Education Attainment Youth and Adults language, Lori Aratani, Research (Box 2, Folder 70)
    - 9/19/99, Education, Stanford Achievement Tests, Research (Box 2, Folder 71)
    - Environment, Lender Romi C, Research (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - 3/18, Environment, San Jose mercury Journalist Jennifer Mena, Research (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - 11/85, Environment Public Safety, Dept of Environmental Planning and Development Division, Plan (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - 4/90, Environment, City of East Palo Alto, Plan (Box 2, Folder 75)
    - 6/95, Environment / Land Use, The Trust for Public Land, Research (Box 2, Folder 76)
    - 11/21/95, Environment / Land Use, Science applications International Corporation, research (Box 2, Folder 77)
    - 12/20, 96, Environment, Palo Alto Weekly, Peter Crauvin Research (Box 2, Folder 78)
    - Soil and Groundwater Investigation at the Ravenswood Industrial Area East Palo Alto, California, Prepared by US Environmental Protection Agency (Box 2, Folder 79)
    - 3/10/97, Environment / Land Use, Cotton / Beland / Associates, Plan (Box 2, Folder 80)
    - 5/97, Environment, San Francisquito Creek, CRMP, Plan (Box 2, Folder 81)
    - 9/97, Environment / Land Use, US Environmental Protection Agency, Research (Box 2, Folder 82)
    - 10/3/97, Environment / Land Use, CRMP Research (Box 2, Folder 83)
    - 3/98, Environment, East Palo Alto, Research (Box 2, Folder 84)
    - 5/98, Environment, CRMP Flood-Erosion Control Task Force, Plan (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - 5/22/98, Environment, City of East Palo Alto, Plan (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - 9/99, Environment, U.S. Environ. Protection Agency, Research (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - 7/19/00, Environment PA Weekly, EnoSarris "East Palo Alto levee" (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Environment, International City/County Management Association, Research (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Environment/Land Use, M. Kirk & C. Wade, Research (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Environment, Romic & CAP, Research (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Environment, Romic Environmental Technologies Porporation, Research (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Environment, Romic, Research (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Environment Land Use, Zinko, Research (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Environment Land Use, UJIMA Sec. Council East Palo Alto, Research (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Environment Land Use, Marilyn Enge Holly Heysur Westersnnol, Research (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Environment Land Use, Tini Tran Dankazak, Research (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Environment, Carolyne Zinko Chronicle Peninsula Bureau, Research (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Environment, San Jose Mercury News, Research (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - 11/2/99, Environment Land se, San Jose Mercury News, Research (Box 3, Folder 15.1)
    - 1983, Health, Community Development Institute, Research (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - 4/30/95, Health, San Mateo County Aids Cases, Research (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - 8/3/98, Health, Packard Children’s HealthVan 11, Research (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - 11/1/98, Health, Blue Ribbon Adv. Grp., Research (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - 1998, Health, Prof. Research Consultants Inc., Research (Pt. 2) (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - 1996, Health, SMC Statistics (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - (empty) (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - (empty) (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - (empty) (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - (empty) (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - 7/5/98, Health, Polaris Research & Development Inc., Research (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - 1998, Health, San Mateo County Board of Supervisors, Research (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - 1/1/99, Health, San Mateo County, Research (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - 2/2/99, Health, Professional Research Consultants Inc., Research (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - 2/25/99, Health, Lucile Packard Children’s Hospital, Research (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - 3/12/99, Health, San Mateo Health Services, Research (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - 4/1/99, Health, San Jose Mercury News, Research (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - 1/15/99, Health, San Mateo County Dept. of Public Health, Research (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - 6/21/99, Health, Packard Children’s HealthVan 11, Plan (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - 8/99, Health Pacific Islander Outreach, Research (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - 10/20/99, Health, S.M. County Human Services Agency, Research (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - 99, Health, Lender: Sally Smith, Research (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - 7/17/01, Health and Human Services, H & H Report Book, Howie Petros (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Health, Jennifer Mena & Marshall Wilson, Research (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Health - Substance Abuse, Title: Summary Needs Assessment of Adults and Youth in East Palo Alto (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - 10/21/83, Housing, Rent Stabilization Task Force, Research (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - 10/24/83, Housing, Western Futures, Research (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - 12/86, Housing, City of East Palo Alto, Plan (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - 10/23/89, Housing, S. Z. Sykes, Rent Stabilization Program, Research (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - 11/20/89, Housing, Horwath, Research (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - 6/8/90, Housing, William Webster, Research (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - 6/14/90, Housing, East Palo Alto05-4, Research (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - 6/14/90, Housing, City of East Palo Alto, Research (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - 9/90, Housing, Lonnie Johnson, Plan (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - 11/30/90, Housing, City of East Palo Alto, Plan (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - 11/91, Housing, The Stanford Center for Study of Homeless Families, Research (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - 5/28/91, Housing, City Hall Council, Research (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - 5/28/91, Housing, City Council Member, Plan/Recomm. (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - 8/91, Housing, Blue Ribbon Commission on Homelessness, Plan (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - 12/14/91, Housing, City of East Palo Alto, Plan (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - 12/91, Housing, The Homeless Family Study, Research (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - 11/30/92, Housing, City of East Palo Alto, Plan (Box 3, Folder 57)
    - 5/92, Housing, S.M. County Peninsula Community Foundation, Plan (Box 3, Folder 58)
    - 5/92, Housing, ABAG Regional Data Center, Research (Box 3, Folder 59)
    - 6/92, Housing, Bostic / Clay / Khoja / Stern, Research (Box 3, Folder 60)
    - 12/20/92, Housing, Times Tribune, Research (Box 3, Folder 61)
    - 8/93, Housing, S.M. Homeless Prevention Task Force, Plan (Box 3, Folder 62)
    - 11/93, Housing, City of East Palo Alto, Research (Box 3, Folder 63)
    - 12/93, Housing, City of East Palo Alto, Plan (Box 3, Folder 64)
    - 3/94, Housing, San Mateo Times, Research (Box 3, Folder 65)
    - 4/94, Housing, City of East Palo Alto, Plan (Box 3, Folder 66)
    - 1/1/95, Housing, CA Dept. of Finance, Research (Box 3, Folder 67)
    - 6/98, Housing, City of East Palo Alto, Plan (Box 3, Folder 68)
    - 5/4/95, Housing Land Use, Local Govt. Commission Conference, Research (Box 3, Folder 69)
    - 8/17/95, Housing, City of East Palo Alto Redevelopment Agency, Plan (Box 3, Folder 70)
    - 11/96, Housing, National Fair Housing Alliance, Research (Box 3, Folder 71)
    - 11/96, Housing, California Reinvestment Committee, Research (Box 3, Folder 72)
    - 97, Housing, Leader: Carol Lamont, Research (Box 3, Folder 73-74)
    - 97, Housing, HUD, Research (Box 3, Folder 75)
    - Housing, CA Dept. of Finance, Research (Box 3, Folder 76)
    - 1/1/98, Housing, California Dept. of Finance, Research (Box 3, Folder 77)
    - 1/98, Housing, Bay Area Economics, Research (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - 3/17/98, Housing, City of East Palo Alto, Plan (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Housing, East Palo Alto CAN DO, Research (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Housing, Don Kazak – D. Sylvester – J. Mena, Research (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Housing, City of East Palo Alto, Research (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - 10/13/99, Housing, Aegis America Real Estate, Research (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - 10/2/99, Housing, San Mateo County Times, Research (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - 3/21/99, Housing, San Jose Mercury News, Research (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - 3/1/99, Housing, San Jose Mercury News, Research (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - 7/99, Housing, East Palo Alto CAN DO, Plan (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - 9/99, Housing, San Mateo Community Info Program, Research (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Housing, CDI Bay / Satterwhite, Plan (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Housing, HUD, Source: Internet Info, Research (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - 6/9/??, Housing, O. Hap Thomson, Research (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - 7/13/97, Housing, Heidi Van Zant, Research (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - 4/11/96, Housing, Tini Tran, Research (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - 3/8/95, Housing, Rufus Jeffris, Research (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - 5/97, Housing, Alison Post, Research (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Housing: History, East Palo Alto Library, Research (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Housing, HUD – UCB Univ. / Comm. Partnerships, Research (1 of 2) (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Housing, HUD – UCB Univ. / Comm. Partnerships, Research (2 of 2) (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - 2/23/00, Housing, Alex Quinn: Household Estimates (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - 4/20/00, Housing, Beverly Purrington "Answers On Housing" (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - 11/16/00, Housing, 1999-2006 Allocation (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - 4/11/01, Housing, Missed Information (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - 110/18/99, Housing, Calvin W., Research (Box 4, Folder 26.1)
    - Land Use, Carolyne Zinko / Chronicle Peninsula Bureau, Research (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - 1990?, Land Use / Environment, County of San Mateo, Plan (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - 11/94, Land Use, National Trust for Historic Preservation, Research (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - 10/30/89, Land Use / Housing, Sun Microsystems, Research / Plan (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - 11/88, Land Use / Public Works, City of East Palo Alto, Report of Plan (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - 12/88, Land Use, City of East Palo Alto, Plan (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - 1/80, Land Use Economics, Stanford Mid-Peninsula Urban Coalition, Plan (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Land Use, Peninsula Library System, Research (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Land Use Economics, Payne-Maxie Consultants / Berkley CA, Plan (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - 11/11/95, Land Use, East Palo Alto Timeline Archive Lists, Research (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - 3/22/96, Neighborhood Assessment Study, SRI Int’l, Research (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - 65, Other History, League of, Research (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - 8/73, Community Plans, Sedway / Cooke Consulting, Plans (Box 4, Folder 39-40)
    - 6/79, Other, Oak Park, Plan (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - 1/6/80, Other: Incorporation, SRI Int’l, Research (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - 4/81, Other: Incorporation, San Mateo Local Formation Commission, Research (Box 4, Folder 43-44)
    - 6/81, Other: Every Category, Dept. of Environ. Mang. Planning & Develop. Division – San Mateo County, Plan (Box 4, Folder 45-46)
    - 9/81, Other: Incorporation, Institute of Govt. Affairs, Research (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - 10/81, Other: Incorporation, SRI Int’l, Research (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - 5/18/82, Community Plans, Dept. of Government Management, Plan (Box 4, Folder 49-50)
    - 12/82, Other: Incorporation, Angus McDonald & Assoc., Research (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - 1983, Other: Incorporation, Angus McDonald & Assoc., Research (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - 7/84, Other: San Mateo County Demographies, The Assoc. of Bay Area Governments, Research (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - 4/85, Other: City of East Palo Alto, Frederick A. Howell, Plan (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - 7/85, Other: City of East Palo Alto, ???, Plan (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - 12/15/86, Other: City Plans, City of East Palo Alto, Plan (Box 4, Folder 56-57)
    - 1998, Other: City Plans, City of East Palo Alto, Plan (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - 1992, Other: Language, John R. Rickford, Research (Box 4, Folder 59)
    - 11/1/93, Other: Menlo Park, The MGT Group Government & Executive Placement Consultants, Plan (Box 4, Folder 60)
    - 2/94, Other: History, San Mateo County Historical Assoc., Research (Box 4, Folder 61)
    - 1994, Other: Language, John R. Rickford, Research (Box 4, Folder 62)
    - 1992, Other: Language, John R. Rockford, Research (Box 4, Folder 63)
    - 1994, Other: General Plan, City of East Palo Alto, Plan (Box 4, Folder 64)
    - 1/95, Other: Community Profile, Cal Poly, Plan (Box 4, Folder 65-66)
    - 4/95, Other: MP, PinPoint Research, Resarch (Box 4, Folder 67)
    - 6/95, Other: Parks & Recreation, Callendar & Sinclair, Plan (Box 4, Folder 68)
    - 8/95, Other: Community Profile, City & Regional Planning 351, Research (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - 9/30/95, Other: Parks & Recreation, Trust for Public Land Sokale / Landry, Plan (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - 10/19/95, Other: Community Plans, East Palo AltoHAS / Urban Ecology / Natl. Park Svc., Plan (Box 5, Folder 3)